export const Questions = [
    {
        question: "When was JavaScript launched?",
        optionA: "1994",
        optionB: "1995",
        optionC: "1996",
        optionD: "2000",
        answer: "1995"
    },
    {
        question: "A function that is passed as an argument is known as a?",
        optionA: "Anonymous Function",
        optionB: "Arrow Function",
        optionC: "Higher Order Function",
        optionD: "Callback Function",
        answer: "Callback Function"
    },
    {
        question: "By which react hook you hold a mutable reference to a value that persists across re-renders?",
        optionA: "useEffect",
        optionB: "useContext",
        optionC: "useRef",
        optionD: "useState",
        answer: "useRef"
    },
    {
        question: "What is a promise in JavaScript?",
        optionA: "It is a native browser API",
        optionB: "It is a built in JavaScript method",
        optionC: "An object that represents the eventual completion or failure of an asynchronous operation",
        optionD: "None of the above",
        answer: "An object that represents the eventual completion or failure of an asynchronous operation"
    },
    {
        question: "How do you export a function in a Node.js module?",
        optionA: "export function() {}",
        optionB: "module.exports = function() {}",
        optionC: "exports.function() {}",
        optionD: "function export() {}",
        answer: "module.exports = function() {}"
    },
    {
        question: "Which module is commonly used to create a server in Node.js??",
        optionA: "http",
        optionB: "https",
        optionC: "net",
        optionD: "tcp",
        answer: "http"
    },
    {
        question: "How do you access data from a POST request in Express (assuming middleware is configured)?",
        optionA: "body-parser",
        optionB: "json-parser",
        optionC: "express-data",
        optionD: "middleware-parser",
        answer: "body-parser"
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is used to define the schema in MongoDB with Mongoose?",
        optionA: "MongoSchema",
        optionB: "mongo.Schema",
        optionC: "SchemaBuilder",
        optionD: "mongoose.Schema",
        answer: "mongoose.Schema"
    },
    {
        question: "Which command is used in MongoDB to retrieve all documents from a collection?",
        optionA: "db.collection.getAll()",
        optionB: "db.collection.findOne()",
        optionC: "db.collection.find()",
        optionD: "db.collection.query()",
        answer: "db.collection.find()"
    },
    {
        question: "How do you define a route with a dynamic parameter in Express?",
        optionA: "app.get('/user#id', ...)",
        optionB: "app.get('/user?id=:id', ...)",
        optionC: "app.get('/user/:id', ...)",
        optionD: "app.get('/user*', ...)",
        answer: "app.get('/user/:id', ...)"
    }
]